Guide to the New York State AFL-CIO Records WAG.031
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - Legislative Session A.9559: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 83)
  - Legislative Session A.9582: Levy, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 84)
  - Legislative Session A.9622: Barraga, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 85)
  - Legislative Session A.9640: Proud, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 86)
  - Legislative Session A.9674A: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 87)
  - Legislative Session A.9707: Griffith, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 88)
  - Legislative Session A.9789: Grannis, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 89)
  - Legislative Session A.9869: Connelly, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 90)
  - Legislative Session A.9871: Healey, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 91)
  - Legislative Session A.9875: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 92)
  - Legislative Session A.9879: Bianchi, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 93)
  - Legislative Session A.9880A: Bragman, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 94)
  - Legislative Session A.9884: Brodsky, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 95)
  - Legislative Session A.9912: Kelleher, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 96)
  - Legislative Session A.9929: Vann, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 97)
  - Legislative Session A.10010: P. Sullivan, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 98)
  - Legislative Session A.10062: Schimminger, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 99)
  - Legislative Session A.10144: Cooke, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 100)
  - Legislative Session A.10179: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 101)
  - Legislative Session A.10220A: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 102)
  - Legislative Session A.10240: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 103)
  - Legislative Session A.10248: Kremer, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 104)
  - Legislative Session A.10352A: Committee on Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 105)
  - Legislative Session A.10635: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 106)
  - Legislative Session A.10639: Burrows, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 107)
  - Legislative Session A.10824: Diaz, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 108)
  - Legislative Session A.10951: Barbaro, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 109)
  - Legislative Session A.10981: Fink, et al., 1984 (Box 35, Folder 110)
  - Legislative Session A.11060: Ferris, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 111)
  - Legislative Session A.11100: Catapano, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 112)
  - Legislative Session A.11117: Patton, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 113)
  - Legislative Session A.11498: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 114)
  - Legislative Session A.11520: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 115)
  - Legislative Session A.11621: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 116)
  - Legislative Session A.11654: Eve, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 117)
  - Legislative Session A.11737: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 118)
  - Legislative Session A.11738: Rules Committee, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 119)
  - Legislative Session A.11780: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 120)
  - Legislative Session A.11850: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 121)
  - Legislative Session A.11877: Rules Committee (Barbaro), 1984 (Box 35, Folder 122)
  - Legislative Session A.11997: Rules, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 123)
  - COPE Files: Phone Banks, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - COPE Files: Special Elections, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - COPE Files: Data Processing NYS Match, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - COPE Files: International Suspense File, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - COPE Files: International Suspense File, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - COPE Files: Labor Conference, Apr 8 1983 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - COPE Files: COPE Coordinating Meeting, Mar 14 1984 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - COPE Files: AFT Executive Council 1984 Convention, Aug 23 1984 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - COPE Files: Pauls Personal Expenses, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - COPE Files: NYS Council of Carpenters Convention, Aug 23-24 1984 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - COPE Files: COPE Advisory Committee Meeting, Aug 26 1984 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - COPE Files: Albany Labor Day Parade, Sep 3 1984 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - COPE Files: Capital District Union Label & Service Trades Council, Sep 8 1984 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - COPE Files: Lynn R. Williams Testimonial Dinner, Sep 10 1984 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - COPE Files: Central Labor Body Presidents, Sep 13 1984 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - COPE Files: Auburn Area Labor Council, Sep 15 1984 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - COPE Files: Dunkirk Labor Council, Sep 18 1984 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - COPE Files: Strategy Meeting of the Labor for Mondale-Ferraro Campaign, Sep 20 1984 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - COPE Files: Mondale-Ferraro Campaign, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - COPE Files: Budget Bills S.7751-8000, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - COPE Files: Budget Bills A.9141-9190, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - COPE Files: COPE, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - COPE Files: Computers, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - COPE Files: Convention, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - COPE National Correspondence, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Phone Banks, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - National COPE (Barkan), 1980 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Election, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Letters requesting AFL-CIO Endorsement, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Labor Committee for Javits 1980 Election (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Coordinators, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Regional Conference (Boston), Mar 9-11 1981 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Regional Conferences (COPE), May 6; 14; 21; 28 1981 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - National COPE (Barkan), 1981 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Council Reports 1980 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Council Budgets 1981 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Council Budgets 1980 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Keypunching Correspondence, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - 1982 Council / Arena Receipts (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - 1981 Council / Arena Receipts (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - 1983 Council Arena Contributions (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Council Budgets 1982 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Council / Arena Receipts 1980 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Assembly Correspondence, undated (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Assembly Election Law Committee, undated (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Regional COPE Meetings, Oct-83 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Regional COPE Meetings: June, Jun-83 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Regional COPE Conferences, Jan 18-21 1983 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - 1982 COPE Training Seminar (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - COPE Advisory Committee Meeting, Nov 17 1983 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting, Mar 14 1983 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - COPE Advisory Committee Meeting, Jul 14 1982 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - 1982 COPE Advisory Committee Meetings (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Senate Correspondence & Business, undated (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Infrastructure Bond Issue 1983 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Legislative Session: NYSUT Convention, Mar 3-9 1986 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Session: EAP, Mar 4 1986 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Session: Metroland Life Insurance Co., Mar 13 1986 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Session: NYS AFL-CIO Staff Meeting, Mar 22 1986 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Session: Marty Rose Testimonial Dinner, Apr 5 1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Session: Learning by Doing Conference, Apr 6-9 1986 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Session: NYS AFL-CIO Legislative Conference, Apr 8 1986 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Session: Community Services Adv. Committee, Apr 9 1986 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Session: Department for Professional Employees, Apr 11 1986 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Session: Labor Education in the Public Schools, Apr 12 1986 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Session: Buffalo AFL-CIO 2nd Annual Appreciation Awards Dinner Dance, Apr 18 1986 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Session: NYSUT WNY Council of Occ. and Special Educators Work, Apr 18-19 1986 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Session: WNYPAC, Apr 21 1986 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Legislative Session: Cornell University EAP, Apr 22 1986 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Session: Community Services Meeting, Apr 23 1986 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Session: Press Conference Americans for a Common Sense Budget, Apr 29 1986 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Session: WNY Directors Meeting, Apr 30 1986 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Session: Staff Meeting, May 2 1986 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Session: MA Fed. of Teachers Convention, May 3 1986 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Legislative Session: Cornell University 40th Annual Celebration, May 3 1986 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Legislative Session: Union Labor & Service Trade Council 59th Convention, May 4-6 1986 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Legislative Session: Northeast Labor Council, May 8-9 1986 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Legislative Session: AFT Executive Board, May 12 1986 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Legislative Session: NYS Labor-Religion Coalition, May 13-14 1986 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Legislative Session: Wateford Teachers Association Rally, May 15 1986 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Legislative Session: Sidney Hillman Awards Luncheon, May 16 1986 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Legislative Session: ED #3 Delegates, May 19 1986 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Session: Rochester CLC Dinner, May 21 1986 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Session: Staff Meeting, May 21 1986 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Legislative Session: Coordinating Comm. for Research in Vocational Education, May 22 1986 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Paul Cole General Files: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Jul 14-26 1986; Sep 22-Dec 11 1986 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Richard Torrey Correspondence, Jan 8 1985; Jun 3 1987 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Paul Cole General Files: COPE, 1984-1987 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Coors, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Convention, Mar 25 1985; Oct 23 1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Convention 1986 Constitution and Amendments (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Community Action, 1984-1986 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Central Labor Councils, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Business Councils, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Building Trades, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Paul Cole General Files: 1987 Budget (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Asbestos Removal, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Articles, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Apha, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Paul Cole General Files: American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Paul Cole General Files: Affiliation, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Asbestos, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Buildings Trades, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Indoor Air Pollution, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Property Taxes, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Pastoral Letter, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Pay by Check, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Pension Investment, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence /Memos: PEC, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Pay Equity, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Prevailing Rate, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Right to Know, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Responsible Bidder, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Resolutions, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Resumes, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Rico, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Safety & Health Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Senate Labor Committee Report, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence /Memos: State Insurance Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence /Memos: State of State 1986 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence /Memos: State of State 1987 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Schedules, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Teachers Memos, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Toxic Tort, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Training Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Transportation Master Plan, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Tax Reform, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Taxes, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Toxic Wastes, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Telephone Calls, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Unemployment Insurance, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Union Health Care Coop (Clinic), 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Workforce, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Wicks Law, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence /Memos: Workshop Series, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Joint Election District Meeting: Buffalo, Dec 10 1984 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Thruway House, Albany, NY, Dec 19 1984 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO State Federation Officers Meeting: Silver Springs, MO, Jan 6-9 1985 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting, Dec 7 1984 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - AFT Standing Committee on Vocational Education: Washington D.C., Fall 1984 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - COPE Files: National AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - COPE Files: NYS AFL-CIO Conference Registration Cards, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - COPE Files: Candidate Endorsements 1982 COPE Adv. Committee, Executive Board & Conference (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - COPE Files: COPE Adv. Meeting: Convention 1982 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - COPE Files: Computer Bills 1982 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - COPE Files: Convention Correspondence, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - COPE Files: COPE Regional Conferences, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - COPE Files: Election 1982 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - COPE Files: Council Endorsements, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - COPE Files: Mario Cuomo, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - COPE Files: 1982 AFL-CIO National Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - COPE Files: Candidates Seeking Endorsements, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - COPE Files: 1982 Candidates (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - COPE Files: NYS Board of Elections Material (Candidates Lists, etc.), 1982 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - COPE Files: Computer Requests, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - COPE Files: Congressional Correspondence, undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - COPE Files: 27th Congressional District Information, undated (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - COPE Files: 1982 Candidates Seeking Endorsements (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - COPE Files: Financial / Activities Report Form, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - COPE Files: 1980 Financial / Activities Reports (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - COPE Files: Union / Council Endorsements, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - COPE Files: Regional Meetings, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - COPE Files: National AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - COPE Files: NYSUT New York State United Teachers, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - COPE Files: NYS Dept. of Labor Correspondence, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - COPE Files: Computer Bills, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - COPE Files: NYS AFL-CIO Correspondence with NYC Office, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - COPE Files: NYC Correspondence, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - COPE Files: National AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - COPE Files: Statistics from Diskettes, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - COPE Files: National COPE Correspondence (Barkan), Jan-81 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - COPE Files: Data Processing Invoices 1979 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - COPE Files: Data Processing Invoices 1981 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - COPE Files: Computer Requests, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - COPE Files: Invoices, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - COPE Files: Constitutional Convention, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - COPE Files: AFL-CIO Convention: Diplomat Hotel, Oct 3-6 1983 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - COPE Files: COPE School, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - COPE Files: COPE Operating Committee, Feb 21-22 1983 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - COPE Files: Campaign Contributions, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - COPE Files: Data Processing Invoices, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - COPE Files: Regional Meetings, Jul 29-31 1980 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - COPE Files: Data Processing Memos International Suspense File, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - COPE Files: Endorsements, 1978; 1980; 1982 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - COPE Files: NYSUT Board of Directors, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - COPE Files: NYSUT, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - COPE Files: American Federation of Teachers, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Legislative Memos: Drug Testing, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Memos: DC 37, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Memos: Department of Labor NYS, 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Memos: Ethics, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Memos: Energy, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Memos: Economic Development, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Memos: Executive Council, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Memos: Financial Services, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Memos: First Source, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Memos: Farmers, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Memos: Hearings, 1986-1987 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Memos: Hospital Corp. of America, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Memos: Industrial Homework, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Legislative Memos: JTPA, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Memos: Job Stabilization, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Memos: Jewish Labor Committee, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Memos: Labor Laws, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Memos: Legislative Report, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Memos: Legislative Program State AFL-CIO, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Legislative Memos: 1987 Conference (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Legislative Memos: Labor Department, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Legislative Memos: Labor Archives, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Legislative Memos: Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Legislative Memos: Minimum Wage, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Legislative Memos: Memos 1986 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Legislative Memos: Memos 1987 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Legislative Memos: NYCOSH, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Memos: National Congress of Employees, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Memos: National AFL-CIO, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Legislative Memos: Occupational Lung Disease, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Legislative Memos: Occupational Disease, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Legislative Memos: OSHA, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Legislative Memos: Officers Report 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Legislative Memos: Part-time Work, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting, May 12 1986 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Cornell University 3rd Annual Conference of Area Labor Adv. Council Members, Jun 2 1986 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - ALMACA Eastern Regional Conference, Jun 8 1986 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - NYS Consumer Assembly, 2nd Annual State-wide Reception and Luncheon, Jun 10 1986 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Vocational Education Committee Meeting, Jun 13-14 1986 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting, Jun 30 1986 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - AFT Convention, Jul 4 1986 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Executive Committee, Jul 9 1986 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Community Services Conference, Jul 17 1986 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting, Jul 25 1986 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Executive Council Meeting, Aug 5 1986 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Labor Roundtable, Aug 11 1986 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Chancery, Aug 14 1986 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Per Capita Letters, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Western NY Directors Meeting NYSUT, Sep 11 1986 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - 12th Annual NYS Apprentice Training Conference, Sep 17 1986 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - NYSUT Board of Directors, Sep 19 1986 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - JTPA Council Conference, Sep 29 1986 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Phone Banks, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Cornell ILR Advisory Council, Oct 1 1986 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting, Oct 1-3 1986 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Executive Council Meeting, Oct 9 1986 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - NYS Labor History Association Awards Reception, Oct 16 1986 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Cornell UCLEAS Conference, Oct 17 1986 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Creator Glens Falls CLC Awards Dinner, Oct 18 1986 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Labor Recognition Dinner, Oct 23 1986 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Lewiston-Porter Central School, Oct 25 1986 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Licensed Practical Nurses SEIU L.721, Oct 28 1986 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Public Employee Relations Board, Oct 29 1986 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Staff Meeting, Oct 29 1986 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Citizens for Tax Justice, Nov 19 1986 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Paul-German Trip, Nov-86 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - AFT Standing Committee on Vocational Education, Nov 21 1986 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - NYS Labor Community Services Meeting, Nov 21 1986 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Teaching International Politics in High Schools Conference, Dec 4-5 1986 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Ethics and Public Policy Group Conference, Dec 4-5 1986 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - NYSUT Board of Directors, Dec 12-13 1986 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - National Trade Union Council Dinner, Dec 16 1986 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - WNY Directors Meeting, Jan 8 1987 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council Meeting, Jan 20-24 1987 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting, Jan 23-24 1987 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Staff Meeting re: Rally, Jan 26 1987 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: AFSCME, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: AFSCME Council #82, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Actors Equity Association, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: ACTWV, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: ATU, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Apprenticeship, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Affiliate Responses, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: DC #37 AFSCME, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Bayberry, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Building Trades, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Carpenters, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Central Bodies, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Chemical Workers, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Federation of Athletes (Pro), 1984 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Firefighters, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Furriers, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Hospital Workers, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: IATSE, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: IUOE Operating Engineers, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: IBEW, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: IBEW Local 817, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: ILGWU, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Insurance Workers, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: IUE, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Labor Lobbyists, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Labor-Religion Coalition, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: 1984 Legislative Conference (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Legislative Reports, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Lie Detectors, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - General Reference/Correspondence: Maritime Port Council, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 30)